so here's the thing yes two things can be true at once and also many things can be true at once i
mean that's what consciousness is having that awareness and understanding the other part of
it is just reality so when we're talking about it on the u.s is not right but either is it on
correct correct correct there's also the reality that everybody got somebody they don't want to
see they don't want it they don't want to and unfortunately that often ends up being two
bad sides so right now we've got two opposing sides that have many layers to them and facets
we've got it on which has absolutely been very repressive to its people and we also have the
united states which is a part of a repressive regime that involves overall oppression of the entire
globe in order for one of them to be taken out the other has to take them out to understand
it on is not up against the united states it on is up against a global oppressive regime that involves
zionists the imf the world bank the vatican that involves many layers and levels and have been in
power for centuries it on is maybe the only way to begin the full destruction of that regime
so do not mistake the desire to see it on defy the efforts of this multi-layered oppressive regime
as some sort of cheering on of oppressors no no no what you are seeing is an understanding
that it takes one bad guy to take out another bad guy so that the rest of us good guys can get to work